ADAPTED FROM DEMON KING
OF JINJIANG LITERATURE CITY
ORIGINAL WORK BY JIULU FEIXIANG
My lord is in
a very dangerous situation now.
His primordial spirit is trapped
in a dream.
A dream?
Yes.
This dream was constructed
with my lord's entire primordial spirit.
And to maintain this dream,
my lord is burning his internal fire,
depleting his primordial spirit.
If he continues like this, I fear…
What do you fear?
I fear that
my lord's primordial spirit will shatter
and he will be obliterated.
Then do something!
That won't happen!
Moon Supreme is immortal.
How could a mere dream trap him?
What if my lord doesn't want to wake up?
What do you mean?
Moon Supreme.
This is bad.
My lord's primordial spirit
is burning even faster!
Shangque, you…
I'm giving him
my primordial spirit's power.
Maybe it can buy us some time.
General, you mustn't.
You will die too
if the spiritual power rebounds.
My lord gave me my life.
Now I am returning it to him.
I'll help too.
Master.
What's wrong?
Hao,
your sword intent is becoming flawed.
In the past,
your sword intent
always had a mortal heart.
But why does it have a killing intent now?
Ever since you were seriously injured,
I've been filled with resentment
toward the Moon Tribe.
I want to destroy the Cangyan Sea.
Maybe that is why my sword intent
has a killing intent now.
Hao, I told you before.
As a warrior,
no matter what you experience
or lose,
you must not be blinded by hatred.
Otherwise, the fighting will never end.
I know.
Lord Changheng.
Right now,
Lord Yunzhong is taking the immortals
to the memorial tablet
to mourn the goddess.
Aren't you going?
The fate you saw in the Tianji Mirror
hasn't come true yet.
Orchid will come back to life.
But…
- My lord.
- Danyin.
Thank you
for telling me everything that you saw
in the Tianji Mirror.
But Orchid
will come back to life.
I will scour the three realms if I must.
No matter the cost,
I will bring her back.
Why are all the Destiny Books
about lovers
that are separated,
never to see each other again?
Look, this one is the same too.
This one too.
Yes.
Fortunately,
the two of us will stay together
and never be apart.
We will never be apart.
Big Blockhead.
Promise me
that you will never leave me, all right?
I promise you.
I will never leave you.
Lord Xunfeng. General.
His internal fire is blazing stronger.
Retract your power
or you will die!
General!
Lord Xunfeng!
General! Lord Xunfeng! Retract your power!
Changheng?
The two tribes have come to a ceasefire.
How dare you come to harm my brother?
Do you think so little of the Moon Tribe?
I'm here to save him.
You?
You're from the Fairy Tribe.
- Lord Xunfeng.
- Dongfang Qingcang is dying.
I don't need to harm him myself.
If you stop me and waste time,
he is bound to die.
Lord Xunfeng.
Saving my lord is more important.
I will enter his dream and wake him up.
If he doesn't wake up
before the incense burns out,
then he is beyond saving.
Changheng?
You…
What did you see?
It's none of your business.
Get out of here.
Tell me.
What did you see in the Tianji Mirror?
I asked you to leave.
Otherwise…
Dongfang Qingcang,
how long will you lie to yourself?
All of this is fake.
It's all a dream!
Nonsense.
Have you really not noticed?
This is just a dream.
You don't want to accept
that Orchid is dead,
so you're escaping from reality
and hiding in your dream like a coward.
Shut up!
She can still come back to life!
Didn't you see it in the Tianji Mirror?
It is a prophecy.
The prophecy hasn't come true yet.
She won't die.
She will come back to life.
Dongfang Qingcang,
I need your help.
Only if you help me
can we save her.
Come out with me.
As long as you leave Arbiter Hall,
you will wake up.
Big Blockhead, where are you going?
See?
Orchid is still alive.
She is my wife now.
Dongfang Qingcang, she is not Orchid.
The real Orchid is dead.
But as long as you leave with me,
we can save her.
Don't listen to him. I'm not dead.
I'm right here.
Dongfang Qingcang, wake up.
She is not Orchid.
She is just your obsession deluding you.
If you continue to stay in this dream,
you will die
from a depleted primordial spirit.
Big Blockhead,
we've been married for 500 years.
Never for a single day
have we been apart.
Do you also suspect me?
The incense has burned up.
All we can do now
is wait.
Leave!
He refuses to wake up.
Don't go.
Please. Don't leave.
Don't go anywhere.
Didn't you promise me
that you would never leave me?
I promised you
I will never leave you.
My lord isn't coming back.
Lord Xunfeng. General.
Don't be so sad.
Moon Supreme, wake up!
- My lord.
Dongfang Qingcang, wake up.
Do you hear me?
- My lord.
Wake up.
You must wake up, my lord!
Big Blockhead.
Don't go.
Look at me.
I'm real.
Touch me.
Feel me.
I'm real.
I'm not a dream.
Wake up!
My lord!
Moon Supreme!
Shangque!
- Shangque!
Calm down!
Lord Xunfeng!
- Moon Supreme!
- My lord!
I knew from the beginning.
You are not real.
I also know this is just a dream.
So
I have to leave.
Don't go.
Please don't abandon me.
We agreed
that we would never be apart.
We will be together forever.
If you bring me back to life,
I will marry someone else.
Do you want to see me marry someone else?
No, I don't.
Don't go.
I'm your wife.
I want to be with you forever.
Don't go.
Orchid.
Wait for me.
I will bring you back to life.
Orchid.
Ronghao.
Are you afraid?
Why are you here?
This place
was built when I was pure-minded.
It's my true love for my master.
You couldn't possibly get in.
Is that so?
Let me tell you.
I did everything you asked me to do.
From now on,
don't bother me and my master again!
You just need to answer me.
Are you afraid?
Afraid?
What am I afraid of?
Are you afraid
that she will learn the truth?
But she will find out sooner or later.
She will find out that her good disciple
has committed atrocious deeds for her,
sullying her with sin and filth
that can never be cleansed.
No.
No!
Master.
Hao,
did you have a nightmare again?
I just dreamed that you were leaving me.
You're talking like a child again.
Go to sleep.
What are you talking about?
I'm the one who got Orchid killed.
It was me.
I took her to the Xuanxu Realm.
I gave her the Chengying Sword.
I watched her kill herself.
What does it have to do with you?
But Fairy Orchid
clearly died
because of the Lord of Haishi.
That's weird.
I am the one drinking.
Why are you drunk?
Are you telling the truth?
Why would I lie to you?
She never stepped foot
outside of the Silent Moon Palace.
Didn't Jieli take Fairy Orchid away?
She tricked me.
- But I--
- General, you mustn't drink.
You just recovered from poison
and to keep my lord alive,
you have drained your primordial spirit.
You mustn't drink.
You should rest well.
Poison?
What poison?
Don't you know, General?
When I was treating you a few days ago,
I found a scar from poison on your nape.
Butterfly-Scale Poison is very lethal.
Fortunately, it had been neutralized,
so I didn't bring it up.
Jieli.
Where have you been?
What took you so long?
It wasn't on purpose.
I just--
Why did you pull on my collar?
She already knew.
Did she detoxify my poison?
Did she save me?
Impossible.
But she is from Haishi.
When it comes to the Bone Orchid,
she is the only one who could have.
What was the reason?
Hao,
what are you hiding from me?
Nothing.
What's wrong?
The music you used to play
was the purest of the three realms.
But now,
it has changed beyond recognition.
What exactly have you been through?
Maybe I have been worrying
about your injuries these days.
- So…
- Lies.
Tell me.
What are you hiding?
I can't tell you.
Please stop asking.
Are you disobeying me now?
I just don't want you
to remember the pain you've forgotten.
Master, didn't you say
that you were tired
of the endless slaughtering
and wanted to retire to the bamboo forest?
Now I have realized it for you.
From now on,
we can live peacefully
in the bamboo forest.
Isn't that good?
What is this place?
This is home.
How could this happen?
Master, do you know?
One swing of the sword
and 30,000 years have passed.
Thirty thousand years?
What happened?
You betrayed me.
- I'll kill you!
- You betrayed me!
- Why are you doing this to me?
- I love you.
Master.
- You betrayed me!
- Master.
Master.
Master, don't listen.
These are your painful memories
from over a thousand lifetimes.
I wanted you to forget,
but when the illusion ends,
they will resurface.
Master, don't listen.
Master.
My bad disciple, Ronghao,
has committed a heinous crime.
He is unforgivable.
I failed to discipline him well.
I should be punished as well.
My lord,
please send us
to the Immortal Slaying Pavilion
to answer for Goddess of Xishan,
the wrongfully massacred Xishan Tribe,
and all living beings
affected by the war in the three realms.
All fault lies with me,
not the former God of War.
Silence.
The goddess is dead.
We cannot lose the God of War again.
At present,
the two tribes have stopped fighting,
but the 100,000 enemy soldiers
have been freed.
God of War, I hope
you can prioritize our overall interests.
You should resume your duties
and continue to protect Shuiyuntian.
God of War.
Please rise.
As for the immortal criminal Ronghao,
take him to Karma Jail
to await punishment.
You can't die yet.
You're useful again.
As expected, you came.
Where is my daughter?
Didn't you ask me here
to give me back my other daughter?
Yes, but…
I have one condition.
I have let Ronghao go once
and repaid his favor.
We are even now.
Give me back my daughter.
How can such a large debt
be written off so quickly?
If you don't save my lord,
I'm afraid
you will never see your daughter again.
As a high god of Shuiyuntian,
how can I allow you
to continue controlling me?
Today,
I shall kill you.
Only I can cure her poison.
If you kill me,
she won't live.
Save my lord for me.
Look.
I gave her back to you alive.
Her mother died for you.
Do you also want to see your daughter die
in front of you?
Father.
She is your daughter?
Am I not your only daughter?
So we are sisters.
Don't touch me.
No wonder I felt close to you
when I saw you in Lucheng before.
Father said
that you're eight minutes older than me.
You are my older sister.
Father.
Didn't you tell me
that Mother was a mortal?
This Moon Tribe woman is full of nonsense.
Lock her up in Karma Jail.
She…
RUINS OF MYRIAD HEAVENS
ARBITER HALL
The Ruins of Myriad Heavens
actually has an Arbiter Hall.
Is Lady Arbiter really inside?
A thousand years ago,
Lady Arbiter released
the convicted dragon, Changyuan,
fell in love, and married him.
They violated heavenly laws.
My brother exacted justice
and imprisoned them here for eternity.
Few people know this secret.
Even Orchid thought
her master was just fond
of the mundane world
and traveling.
And you kept it from her.
The Ruins of Myriad Heavens
is the place of nirvana
beyond the three realms.
Living beings cannot leave after entering
and have
only a galaxy of stars for company.
Even I don't know
if Lady Arbiter is still alive.
I didn't tell Orchid
because I didn't want her to be sad.
If she doesn't know,
then she can still have hope.
Orchid once told me
that her master had a Soul-Painting Brush
that can draw anything in the three realms
and turn it into reality.
This Arbiter Hall
must have been drawn by her.
Drawn?
Then were the fireflies that guided us
and the boat that carried us
also drawn by her?
There was more.
The flower cakes on the boat
are the same as the ones
that Orchid once made for me.
She knows.
She knows everything.
It seems
that Lady Arbiter knew you would come.
The fireflies were a gift
that you gave to Orchid.
Lady Arbiter also knew you would come.
Let's go.
There you are.
Are you Lady Arbiter?
CHANGYUAN
Changyuan.
LADY ARBITER
Beat him up.
You are the Moon Supreme.
Why didn't you dodge?
I am the one who wronged her.
One hit is nothing.
As long as she can be resurrected,
what does it matter
if I must give up my life?
The future is ever-changing.
There is still a chance
in a desperate situation.
If you know this,
Orchid has a chance to be resurrected.
Please enlighten me.
This chance
had been planted
when you two first met.
The first time
we met?
At the Haotian Tower,
she used her goddess power
to gather your primordial spirit.
So she has been saving me
since we first met.
And I have been hurting her.
What is the use
in saying this now?
Fortunately,
a wisp of Orchid's primordial spirit
is merged with your primordial spirit.
To resurrect her,
we need to remove her primordial spirit,
nurture it in the Holy Land of Xilan,
and wait for her to take form.
All right.
Go.
One more thing.
Please enlighten me.
Go ahead.
Dongfang Qingcang and Fairy Danyin
both looked into the Tianji Mirror.
They both saw
Orchid and I getting married
along the Oblivion River.
I've tried so many times,
but I've never seen it.
There is nothing in the Tianji Mirror.
Everything shown in the mirror
is a prophecy.
Those who can see this prophecy
are the ones
who can bring about this marriage.
Is the future in the Tianji Mirror
truly unalterable?
Yes.
It cannot be altered.
Changheng,
the next time you come,
remember to bring plenty of fine wine.
Thank you, Lady Arbiter.
You.
Come here.
Take this.
A Destiny Book.
This is Orchid's Destiny Book.
Don't be silly.
You're not ordinary in the least.
Even if I place you among 100,000 orchids,
I can find you
in an instant.